Phoebe::Oh hey, Joey.
;嘿, Joey
Phoebe::Listen, I need to ask you sth.
;我有点事要跟你商量
Phoebe::Ok, you know how my step-dad's in prison?
;你还记得我继父在监狱里的事吧?
Phoebe::Yeah, well, listen, he was supposed to get a weekend furlough so he could come to the wedding tomorrow.
;恩，这个周末他本来有个假期的, 这样明天他就能来参加我的婚礼了
Phoebe::But he just called and uhm, well apparently, stabing iceman in the exercise yard, just couldn't wait until Monday.
;但是他刚刚打电话来说，嗯， 他在操场上捅了一个送冰的家伙 他就不能忍到礼拜一吗！
Joey::So he can't come? Phoebe::No.
;这么说他来不了了吗? 对
Phoebe::And so there's no one to walk me down the aisle. And uh,
;这么一来就没人挽着我走过红地毯了所以，嗯...
Phoebe::well, I'd just really love it if you would do it.
;嗯，我很希望你能挽着我
Joey::Seriously?
;真的?
Phoebe::Yeah, you, you know, you've sorta been like a dad to me.
;对，你知道，一直以来我都把你当作父亲一样
Phoebe::I mean, you've always, you know, looked doubt for me and shared your wisdom.
;我是说，你一直以来都很照顾我， 和我一起分享你的智慧
Joey::I'm pretty wisdomas.
;我的确很有智慧
Phoebe::So, what do you say?
;所以...你觉得呢?
Joey::Are you kidding? Phoebe, I would be honored.
;当然，这是我的荣幸，Phoebe
Phoebe::Oh, thank you.
;哦，谢啦
Phoebe::I hope, I hope you know how much you mean to me.
;我希望你能够了解你对我来说有多么重要
Joey::Listen, I hope, I hope you know...
;听着，我希望，我希望你知道...
Joey::I don't want you see your father crying. Go to your room!
;我不想让你看到爸爸哭的样子 回自己的房间去!
Joey::Oh, no, no. Let your dad get this.
;哦，别，别，别，让爸爸来付
Phoebe::Oh, it's my wedding planner. She's driving me crazy.
;哦，是我的婚礼策划人她快把我逼疯了
Phoebe::Hello. Hey, ok, stop screaming!
;喂，嘿，ok, 行了行了，别这么大声嚷嚷!
Phoebe::Ok, so halibut.
;Ok, 那就比目鱼好了
Phoebe::Alright, so salmon, either way, I don't know. It doesn't matter to me.
;好吧，三文鱼也行, 随便什么都好 我无所谓
Monica::Well, it matters to me!
;可我有所谓!
Phoebe::Well, I don't care, so you pick.
;好吧，我不在乎，听你的好了
Monica::Did you just hang up on me?
;你刚才挂我的电话来着?
Monica::Alright, look. I need you at the rehearsal dinner tonight at 18:00.
;好了，听着，我要你在晚上十八点 整的时候准时到达婚礼彩排的现场
Phoebe::Uhuh, ok, what time is that?
;好, 那是几点钟啊?
Monica::You don't know military time?
;你不知道军用时刻（24小时制）吗?
Phoebe::Well, I must have been in a missile training the day they taught that.
;哦，当时我在接受导弹训练，所以没学到
Monica::Just subtract twelve.
;减12就行了
Phoebe::Ok. So 1800-12 is 1788. Monica::6:00!
;好. 那1800减去12就是1788 6点钟!
Monica::Oh, hold on. Yeah, Galler here.
;哦，等一下好, 我是Geller
Monica::No, I said it has to be there by 5:00, goodbye.
;不, 我说过了，一定要在5点之前送到再见
Monica::God, how hard is it to make an ice sculpture?
;天哪，做一个冰雕有那么难么?
Phoebe::Ice sculpture? That sounds really fancy. I told you I just want a simple wedding.
;冰雕? 太隆重了吧 我跟你说过我只想要一个简单的婚礼就好
Monica::Please, honey. Leave the datails to me.
;放心好了, 亲爱的一切都包在我身上
Monica::Now I want to make this day as special for you as I can.
;为了你，我会尽量把这一天弄得特别一些
Monica::Now ok, I was thinking that the Harbors should wear white.
;好了, 我打算让港湾乐队(the Harbours) 穿成白色
Phoebe::Harbors? My friend Margery is playing the steel drums.
;港湾乐队? 不是我朋友Margery来敲钢鼓的吗?
Monica::Oh, she backed out.
;哦, 她退出了
Phoebe::She did? Why?
;她退出了? 为什么?
Monica::I made her.
;我叫她这么做的
Monica::Steel drums don't really say elegant wedding. Nor does Margery's overwhelming scent.
;钢鼓和高雅的婚礼不太搭调， 而且Margery的体味太浓了
Phoebe::Hey! She will shower when Tibet is free.
;嘿! 西藏独立之后她会洗澡的
Chandler::Hey. You look great.
;嘿你看起来真美
Chandler::I'm so glad we're having this rehearsal dinner, you know?
;我真高兴在婚礼之前能有这么一次彩排
Chandler::I so really get to practice my meals before I eat them.
;我打算在把这些食物吃下去之前 好好跟它们演习一下
Phoebe::Hey, what did we say it was your one gift to us.
;嘿, 还记得你答应过要送给我们 的礼物是什么吗？
Chandler::No stupid jokes. But, I thought that was for the actual wedding.
;不开无聊的玩笑 我以为那只是在正式的婚礼上
Phoebe::Rehearse it.
;先演习一下吧
Ross::Hi.
;嗨
Mike::Thanks for coming, you guys.
;真高兴你们都来了
Ross::Oh, I... I was going for a handshake.
;哦, 我... 我只打算握个手
Mike::Is that why your hand is pressed against my crotch?
;所以你把手顶在我的裤裆上?
Ross::That is why.
;没错
Phoebe::So, Rach, where is Emma?
;好了, Rach, Emma呢?
Rachel::Oh, Monica made me send her to my mother's.
;哦, Monica让我把她送到我妈那里去了
Rachel::Apparently, babies and weddings don't mix.
;显然，婴儿和婚礼可掺合不到一块儿
Monica::Are you still crying about your damn baby?
;你还在为你那烦人的小家伙哭哭啼啼的?
Monica::Phoebs, you gotta keep the line moving. Remember, 20 seconds per person.
;Phoebe, 待会儿（在致酒时）你要说快点 记住，跟每个人都是20秒
Monica::You see these clowns all the time.
;你和这些家伙天天见面，（没什么可说的）
Joey::Hey, you're Mike's parents, right?
;嘿, 你们是Mike的父母吧?
Mike's mom::Yes, we are.
;是的
Joey::Our little ones are grown up fast, aren't they?
;眼看着我们的小家伙们都长这么大了，是吧？
Mike's dad::How's that?
;你说什么?
Joey::You know, on the one hand, you're happy for them, but on the other hand, it's hard to let go.
;我们做父母的，一方面替他们感到高兴, 但另一方面，心里又难免有点舍不得
Mike's dad::Who in God's name are you?
;你到底是谁啊?
Joey::Hey I'm not fond of you, either, ok? But at least I was just trying to be nice for the kids.
;嘿，我也不喜欢你们，好? 我是看在孩子们的面子上才跟你们客气的
Chandler::You know what I just realized?
;你知道我刚想起什么吗?
Chandler::We have no idea what we're doing in the wedding tomorrow.
;咱俩还没有被分配在婚礼上的任务呢
Ross::Yeah, I thougt we'd be groomsmen. But wouldn't they've just asked us by now?
;对啊，我觉得咱们会是伴郎 但都到这会儿了，他们怎么还不跟咱俩说呢?
Ross::When did they ask you to be a bridesmaid?
;你什么时候知道你是伴娘的?
Rachel::Uh... November?
;呃... 11月?
Ross::I wanna say it's not looking good.
;我觉得情况有点不妙
Rachel::Hey, Phoebs? Phoebe::Sorry?
;嘿, Pheebs? 干吗?
Rachel::Uh, you haven't told these guys what they are doing in the wedding yet.
;呃, 你还没有告诉他们俩在婚礼上要做什么呢
Phoebe::Uhm, well, they're not in the wedding. Ross::What?
;哦, 那个, 他们不会出现在婚礼仪式上 什么?
Rachel::Well, this is really awkward.
;呃, 气氛有点尴尬
Rachel::Oh, and I can leave.
;哦, 这儿没我的事儿了
Phoebe::I'm sorry, you guys. But you know, Mike has got his brother and his friends from school, so, you know.
;真对不起你们，但Mike有一个哥哥， 而且还有他在学校的死党, 所以...
Phoebe::You were, if it helps, you were next in line. You just miss the khi.
;如果这么说能让你们好受一点, 你们两个是头号候补， 就差那么一点
Ross::Oh, man.
;哦, 天哪
Chandler::This is like Figure Skating Team all over again.
;以前在选花样滑冰队员（女子运动项目） 的时候就是这样
Chandler::I mean Synchronized Swimming.
;我是说，水上芭蕾（还是女子运动项目）
Chandler::I mean the Balance Beam.
;我的意思是，平衡木（仍旧是女子运动项目）
Chandler::Help me.
;帮帮忙
Ross::Football! Chandler::Thank you.
;橄榄球! 谢了
Monica::Oh, Phoebs, spit that out. That has pork in it.
;噢, Phoebe, 赶快吐出来那里面有猪肉
Phoebe::I thought the pot stew is supposed to be vegetarian.
;我记得那个砂锅应该是全素的
Monica::Yeah, I changed them. I sent you a fax about it.
;啊, 是的，但我做了点变动我发传真告诉你了
Phoebe::Well, I don't have a fax machine.
;可是我根本没有传真机啊
Monica::Huh! Well there are going to be a few surprises.
;哈! 那你可能会发现有一些意外
Ross::I can't believe we're gonna be the only people that aren't in this way.
;我简直不敢相信， 只有我们俩个不会出现在仪式上
Chandler::I know, I hate being left outta things.
;是啊，我讨厌被冷落
Ross::And it's a wedding! It'll be weird if I'm not in it.
;要知道这是一个婚礼! 如果缺了我感觉会很奇怪的
Mike::Hey, guys, how's it going?
;嘿, 你们俩怎么样?
Chandler::Fine. We're just sitting here, alone, doing nothing.
;还好啦这不，我们正坐着呢， 就我们俩，无所事事
Chandler::It's our rehearsal for tomorrow.
;我们在为明天做彩排呢
Mike::Hey look, about tomorrow, I've got a question for you.
;嘿，关于明天，我有个问题问你们
Mike::I just found out that one of my groomsman had an emergency and can't make it.
;我刚知道我的一个伴郎出了点急事， 所以不能来了
Chandler::What happened? Ross::Who cares! And?
;出什么事了? 管那么多干嘛! 所以...?
Mike::And I was wondering if, you know, maybe one of you guys...
;所以我在想，也许你们两个人中的一个能...
Ross::I'll do it! Chandler::No, no. Me, me!
;我来替他! 不, 不我, 我!
Mike::You both wanna do it? Uh, there's only room for one.
;你们两个都想做? 呃, 只有一个名额
Chandler::Pick me! I look great in tux and I will not steal focus.
;选我! 我适合穿燕尾服， 而且我这模样也不会抢你的镜头
Ross::No, Mike, no. You wanna pick me!
;不, Mike, 不选我!
Ross::I mean, watch!
;我的意思是, 瞧!
Ross::Uhm, I really don't feel very comfortable making this decision.
;呃, 我不太习惯来做这种决定
Mike::You know, Phoebe knows you better, I'm gonna let her chose.
;Phoebe更了解你们, 我会让她来选
Ross::Well, if Phoebe's choosing, then say hello to Mike's next groomsman.
;嗯，如果是Phoebe来选的话, 你现在就可以跟Mike的新伴郎打招呼了
Chandler::Oh, I will. But I'll need a mirror, as he is me.
;哦, 我会的但我要先找一面镜子， 因为这个人就是我
Ross::Please, you're going down. Chandler::You're going downer.
;省省吧, 你逊死了 你更逊
Ross::Is that what they say on the Figure Skating Team?
;他们在选花样滑冰队员的时候就是这么说你的？
Chandler::I wouldn't know, I didn't make it.
;我不知道，我没被选上
Joey::So you know I'm fulfilling Phoebe's step-dad tomorrow, right?
;明天我会扮演Phoebe的继父, 你知道吧?
Mike::Yeah. Thanks for doing that.
;知道很感谢你能这么做
Joey::Oh, hey, my pleasure.
;哦，嘿，这是我的荣幸
Joey::So what are your intentions with my Phoebe?
;那好，你对我的Phoebe有什么企图?
Mike::I intend to marry her.
;我“企图”跟她结婚
Joey::Oh, a wise acher.
;哦，你这一拳打得还挺聪明
Joey::Now I understand you planned to support your wife by playing the piano.
;照我的理解，你似乎打算靠弹钢琴来养活老婆
Joey::It's kinda unstable.
;这种工作好像不太稳定
Mike::No more so than acting.
;哦，跟演戏比起来还算好啦
Joey::Strike 2.
;第二拳
Mike::You're right. She probably will support me.
;你说得对我可能需要她来养活
Mike::Hey, unless we move in with you, dad.
;嘿, 除非我们搬去跟你一起住, 爸爸
Joey::Strike 3.
;第三拳
Joey::You only get one more, Mike.
;你只有最后一次机会了，Mike
Ross::So? What did you decide?
;怎么样? 你决定了没有?
Phoebe::I decided to pee.
;我决定...要去厕所
Chandler::Mike didn't tell you?
;Mike没跟你说吗?
Chandler::You have to choose one of us to be in your wedding, one of your groomsman fell out.
;有个伴郎来不了了， 你要在我们两个人里选一个来代替他参加仪式
Phoebe::Oh, no. I can't choose between you two. I love you both so much.
;哦, 不你们两个叫我怎么选啊 你们对我来说同样重要
Chandler::Just not enough to put us in the original wedding party.
;的确重要，差一点就能参加原定的婚礼了
Phoebe::I don't wanna choose. It's...
;我没法选这太...
Phoebe::Oh, ok, wait. Rach!
;哦, 好, 等一下Rach!
Phoebe::Uhm, listen, I have a very special bridesmaid test for you to give.
;呃, 我需要你作为伴娘替我选样东西
Rachel:: Goody! What is it?
;太棒了! 选什么?
Phoebe::Well, there is a spot open for one groomsman and you have to choose between Ross and Chandler. So, good luck with that.
;嗯, 现在伴郎有一个空缺， 你需要在Ross和Chandler中间选一个 所以...祝你好运
Rachel::What, what? No, no, I don't wanna do that.
;什么, 什么? 不, 不要, 我不想选这个
Phoebe::Alright, I guess I have to find a new bridesmaid.
;好吧, 我想我只好去另找一个新的伴娘了
Ross::I'll do it!
;我来!
Monica::Ok, it's 21:00. Time for your toasts.
;好, 现在是21:00到你敬酒的时间了
Mike::Do I have a minute to go to the bathroom?
;我能不能先去一下洗手间?
Monica::You had a bathroom break at 20:30. Pee on your own time, Mike.
;你的小便时间是20:30 要专时专用, Mike
Monica::Now.
;现在
Monica::In regard to the toasts, ok? You wanna keep them short.
;关于致酒词，要尽量简短一些
Monica::Nothing kills a rehearsal dinner like long speeches. Ok.
;婚礼彩排的时候， 没有什么比又臭又长的致酒词更烦人了
Monica::You just get in, do your thing and get out.
;你要做的就是：上场，干活，然后走人
Mike::Is that what you said to Chandler?
;你跟Chandler也这么说?
Monica::It's 21:01, and I'm not amused.
;现在已经21:01了, 而且我一点也不觉得好笑
Monica::The bride and groom have a few words they like to say.
;新郎和新娘要说“两”句
Phoebe::Ok. Hello, everyone, and thank you all for being here tonight.
;好. 嗨，大家好, 很高兴各位今晚能够光临
Phoebe::So, tomorrow is the big event.
;明天就是正式的婚礼了
Phoebe::And some of might not know, but Mike and I didn't get off to the best start.
;大家可能还不知道，我和Mike的开始 一点也不精彩
Phoebe::Uhm, yeah. My friend Joey and I decided to fix each other up with friends.
;呃, 是这样的当时Joey和我决定 相互替对方介绍朋友
Phoebe::So, I, I...
;所以呢, 我, 我...
Phoebe::I... I gave it a lot thought and I fixed him up with my friend Marialen who couldn't be here tonight because...
;我... 我当时仔细考虑了半天，然后决定 把我的朋友Marialen介绍给他 Marialen今晚没有来，因为她...
Phoebe::Which is not important, she is in rehab...
;这不重要，她...
Phoebe::Anyway, so Joey said he was fixing me up with his friend Mike only he didn't have a friend Mike,
;总之呢, Joey说他要介绍他的朋友Mike给我认识， 但他并不认识什么叫Mike的朋友
Phoebe::so he just brought, uh, my Mike, and...
;所以他呢，就把我的Mike, 呃，带去了，然后...
Phoebe::But despite... you know, it got, it got good.
;尽管如此... 呃, 结果呢，结果还不错.
Phoebe::Ok, I wanna take a moment to metion my mother who couldn't be here for...
;好, 我想要在这里用一点点时间来缅怀一 下我的母亲她今晚不能出席，因为...
Monica::Oh, god.
;哦, 天哪
Phoebe::And, and moment is over. So, ok, uhm...
;呃, 缅怀时间结束好了，好, 呃...
Phoebe::Oh no, forget that, I can firget that, and uh...
;哦, 这个就不说了, 我可以跳过这里, 然后...
Phoebe::Oh, this is funny, oh but you need to know that...
;哦, 这个很有意思, 哦但首先你得知道...
Phoebe::Oh, well ok, I...
;哦, 好吧，好, 我...
Phoebe::Ok, Monica, I can't do it like this!
;好, Monica, 我再也受不了了!
Phoebe::This is my wedding! Ok? I don't wanna this, or this, or this, ok?
;这是我的婚礼! 好? 我不需要这样, 或者这样, 或者这样, 好?
Phoebe::I just wanted a simple wedding where my fiance can go to the bathroom any time he wants!
;我要的只是一个简单的婚礼， 我要我的未婚夫能够随心所欲地上厕所!
Phoebe::You know what? You're done.
;你知道吗，你玩完了
Monica::What? Phoebe::You're fired!
;什么? 你被炒了!
Phoebe::Cheers!
;干杯!
Phoebe::Hey! Rachel::Happy wedding day!
;嘿! 新婚快乐!
Phoebe::Oh, happy my wedding day to you.
;哦, 也祝你快乐
Rachel::Ok, Joey, listen, this is going to be bridesmaid centre, alright?
;好, Joey, 听着, 从现在开始， 这里是伴娘的地盘，明白了吗?
Rachel::We're gonna have hair makeup going on in bathroom, and...
;我们要在卫生间里面做头发，然后...
Rachel::Oh, I had to move a couple of things in the frige to make room for the corsages.
;哦, 我要把冰箱里的东西挪一下， 给襟花腾出地方
Joey::Oh, man! I wouldn't have breakfast if I knew there's gonna be corsages.
;噢, 真是的! 早知道有襟花我就不吃早饭了
Monica::Uh, about last night,
;呃, 关于昨晚
Monica::I know you're under a lot of stress and...
;我知道你压力很大，所以...
Monica::Even though that the things you said hurt me a little bad.
;尽管你说的话让我有点伤心
Monica::My point is... Well, I'm willing to take my job back.
;我的意思是... 好吧, 我愿意复职
Phoebe::Oh, well, that's ok.
;哦, 还是算了吧
Phoebe::I think you and I will do much better if you're just, you know, as bridsmaid.
;我觉得如果你只做伴娘的话情况会好得多
Monica::Well, if you say so, ok.
;哦，既然你这么说，好
Monica::If that's really what you want and here, I give you the headset.
;如果你真这么想的话，好吧， 给你这个耳机
Monica::I don't really wanna give you the headset.
;我还是不太想给你这个耳机
Monica::And I guess if you're taking over, then you should probably return these messages.
;还有就是，如果你要接手的话, 你大概需要回复这些信息
Phoebe::Wow, this is a lot.
;哇, 真不少啊
Monica::But I'm sure you can handle this.
;我相信你能处理它们
Monica::I mean I have won awards for my orgnizational skills but,
;我是说，尽管我曾经获得过组织技能 的证书，但是呢
Monica::I'm sure you'll do fine.
;我相信你肯定没问题
Phoebe::You've won awards?
;你获得过证书?
Monica::I printed it on my computer.
;是我用自己的电脑打印出来的
Ross::Hey. Monica::Hi.
;嘿 嗨
Ross::Where is Rach?
;Rach呢?
Monica::She's in her room, why?
;她在自己的房间, 有事吗?
Ross::I have to talk to her about this groomsman situation, ok?
;我要跟她谈谈关于那个伴郎的问题, 好?
Ross::I'm not gonna watch Chandler up there while I'm sitting in the seat like some chump.
;我可不想像个傻子一样坐在那儿 看着Chandler在婚礼上露脸
Ross::Ah, my God, you're breathtaking.
;啊, 天哪, 你简直美得令人窒息
Rachel::What do you want?
;你想干嘛?
Ross::You haven't by any chance chosen the groomsman yet, have you?
;你还没决定伴郎的人选吧?
Rachel::Oh, Ross, come on, please. Don't make it harder than it already is.
;哦, Ross, 求你了 我已经很为难了，你就别再添乱了
Ross::I'm not. I'm making it easier, pick me!
;我没有啊我是在让事情简单化, 选我!
Rachel::Well, Chandler said that it's really important for him, too.
;可是, Chandler也说这个机会对他十分重要
Ross::Listen, whoever you pick is gonna walk down the aisle with you.
;听着, 无论你选谁，你要知道 你选的这个人将要跟你一起走过红地毯
Ross::Now I promise I won't say a word, but if you pick Chandler,
;我可以保证，到时候我一个字也不会说， 但如果你选Chandler的话
Ross::he's gonna be whistling stupid jokes in your ear the whole time.
;他肯定会一直在你耳朵旁边嘀咕他那些 无聊的玩笑
Rachel::Oh, you're the less of two evils.
;哦, 那倒是他比你还祸害
Phoebe::Stan, I don't understand what you're saying.
;Stan, 我不知道你在说什么
Phoebe::What is wrong with the flowers? Lorgans? What the hell are lorgans?
;花又有什么问题了? Lorgans? Lorgans是什么见鬼的玩意?
Monica::I know.
;我知道
Mike::Hey.
;嘿
Phoebe::Listen, Mike, if you were swedish, and you were saying the word lorgans, what flower will that be?
;嘿, Mike, 如果你是瑞典人, 你用lorgans 来代表一种花, 会是什么花呢?
Mike::Orchids? Phoebe::Right there, that's why I'm marrying you.
;兰花(Orchids)? 真棒，我就是因为这个才嫁给你的
Joey::Hello, Michael.
;你好, Michael
Mike::Joseph.
;Joseph
Joey::May I have a word with you, please?
;我能跟你说两句吗?
Mike::This is... great.
;这里真是... 棒极了
Joey::Have a seat.
;坐
Joey::Last night, I tried to welcome you into my family.
;昨天晚上, 我试着欢迎你进入我们的家族
Joey::Instead, you disrespected me. I can not allow this.
;然而，你对我很不尊重我不能容忍这一点
Mike::Are you rehearsing for some really bad mafia movie?
;你是在排练什么劣制黑社会电影吗?
Joey::More back talk.
;还敢顶嘴
Joey::And yes, I maybe borrowing a few lines from my recent unsuccessful audition for Family Onitu, this time isn't personal.
;没错，最近我是参加了一次《Onitu家族》续集的试镜, 我从剧本中挑了两句
Mike::Joey, I kinda have a little lot to do today, what do you want?
;Joey, 我今天比较忙, 你到底想要干嘛?
Joey::I want you to take this seriously.
;我想要你认真一点
Joey::Phoebe is very, very important to me, ok?
;Phoebe对我来说非常非常的重要, 好?
Joey::And I wanna make sure that you are gonna take care of her.
;我要你保证，你会好好照顾她
Mike::Joe, I love Phoebe.
;Joe, 我爱Phoebe
Mike::She's the sigle most important thing in my life. I'd die before I let anything happen to her.
;在我的生命中没有什么比她更重要 我宁死也不会让她受到任何伤害
Joey::That's what I wanted to hear.
;这才是我想听的
Joey::Because she's family, ok? And now you're gonna be family.
;因为我当她是家里人，好? 现在你也要成为家里的一份子了
Joey::And there's nothing more important in the whole world than family.
;在世界上没有什么事比家庭更重要
Mike::That must have been one lousy movie. Joey::That was me!
;那个电影可真是烂得可以 不是台词，是我说的!
Chandler::Hey, can I talk to you about the groomsman thing?
;嘿,我能跟你商量一下伴郎的事吗？
Chandler::If you pick Ross, you know, he'll walk you down the aisle just fine.
;如果你选Ross,你知道的, 你们俩只能安安静静地走过红地毯
Chandler::But if you choose me, you'll be getting some comedy.
;但如果你选我的话，你可就有乐子听了
Rachel::Even so,
;即便如此
Rachel::I think I'm gonna pick Ross.
;我想我还是选Ross
Chandler::Let me tell you why you need to pick me.
;我来告诉你为什么你要选我
Chandler::See, when I was a kid, I was always left outta everything.
;当我还是个孩子的时候，无论做什么 我总是被冷落的一个
Chandler::you know, and it really made me feel insecure.
;你要知道，这种经历总是让我缺乏安全感
Chandler::I was always picked last in gym,
;在运动场上我永远都是被人家挑剩下的那个
Chandler::even behind the big fat exchange student who didn't even know the rules to baseball.
;就算是那个交换学生，那个连什么是棒球也 不知道的傻大个儿也排在我前面
Chandler::I mean, this guy would strike out and then run to third.
;那个家伙一打着球，撂下球棒就朝三垒上跑
Chandler::Anyway, if I'm the only one left outta this wedding,
;总之，如果我成为唯一一个不能参加婚礼的人
Chandler::I just know that all those old feelings are gonna come rushing back.
;以前那些凄惨的回忆就会再次浮现在眼前
Rachel::Alright, fine, I pick you.
;好吧，我选你
Chandler::Make groom for Chandler.
;终于有Chandler的一席之地了
Rachel::Oh, my!
;噢, 我的天哪!
Phoebe::No, we're gonna do it my way.
;不, 要照我说的做
Phoebe::Because your way is stupid.
;因为你的办法太笨了
Phoebe::Alright, I gotta go, I have another call reverend.
;好了，有电话正打进来，我要挂了，牧师
Phoebe::Hello.
;喂
Joey::I'm glad we have this little talk. Mike::Yes, yeah.
;这次小小的谈话还算愉快 是啊, 没错
Mike::And thanks for all the wedding night advice.
;对了，谢谢你关于洞房的那些建议
Mike::That didn't make me uncomfortable at all.
;我一点都不觉得尴尬
Mike::Alright, it's all. See everybody tonight.
;好了，就这样吧大家晚上见喽
Mike::Uh, did you guys know that there's a giant ice sculpture in the hall?
;呃, 你们知道在走廊里有个大号的冰雕么？
Phoebe::Oh my god, what's it doing here?
;哦天哪，为什么会在这儿的？
Monica::Ah, I guess it got sent to the billing addr as apposed to shipping addr.
;呃, 我猜是送货的家伙把投递地址 和付款人地址搞混了
Monica::Oh, What a pickle!
;哦, 真是个蠢货!
Phoebe::Oh my god! Everything is such a mess. Why is this happening to me?
;我的天哪! 什么事都是一团糟 为什么这些事情会发生在我身上？
Joey::How bad do you wanna stick you tongue on that?
;你们想不想用舌头去舔舔它?
Chandler::How's it going?
;你怎么样?
Ross::Good. I'm just getting some coffee, so I'm alert for the wedding.
;我很好啊我来要点咖啡喝， 这样我能在婚礼上清醒一点
Chandler::That's what I was doing, too.
;我也是这么打算的
Ross::Well, you have fun tonight.
;那好，今晚玩得高兴点
Chandler::You, too. Ross::Oh, I will.
;你也是 哦, 我会的
Chandler::Me, too.
;我也会的
Ross::Wait a minute, I know why I'm being such an ass, why you?
;慢着, 我知道自己为什么这么得意 但你为什么也这样？
Chandler:: I'm not supposed to tell you.
;我不能告诉你
Chandler::You told us both we could be in the wedding?
;你同时答应我们两个人参加仪式？
Rachel::Well, in my defence, you weren't supposed to tell each other!
;我的解释是, 你们不应该告诉对方的!
Ross::Rachel, only one of us can do it. You have to choose.
;Rachel, 只有一个人可以参加婚礼仪式 你必须要选一个
Ross::ou and me, together again.
;你和我, 我们又能在一起了
Chandler::Rach, Rach, knock, knock.
;Rach, Rach, 咚, 咚（敲门声）
Rachel::Who's there? Chandler::I'll tell you at the wedding.
;是谁啊? 在婚礼上我再告诉你
Mike::Hey. I forgot my scarf.
;嘿，我忘戴围巾了
Rachel::Well, you know what, I can't do this, I don't know which one of you guys to pick.
;我做不来，我真的不知道应该选谁
Mike::Oh, you haven't picked yet. Oh, good, 'cause I had an idea.
;哦，你还没选好呢我倒是有个好主意
Mike::I thought it would be fun if the third groomsman was my family dog Chappy.
;我觉得如果由我们家的狗Chappy来担任伴郎的话 肯定很有意思
Ross::What, a dog? No, Rachel gets to choose.
;什么, 一只狗? 不, 让Rachel来选
Rachel::Well, this is a tough one.
;真是难以抉择啊
Rachel::I think I'm gonna have to go with the dog.
;看起来我只有选那只狗了
Phoebe::Alright, wait, so what you're saying is the chef is at the Hamilton Club but the food is not,
;等一下，你是说，厨子已经到Hamilton俱乐部了， 但食物还没有送到？
Phoebe::and the drinks are there but the bartender is not?
;饮料和酒水已经送到了，但男招待还没有到？
Phoebe::Are... are you frigging kidding me!?
;你... 他妈的开什么玩笑!?
Monica::How's it going?
;怎么样了?
Phoebe::Help me. Monica::What?
;帮帮我... 什么?
Phoebe::I want you to be crazy bitch again.
;我想让你做回疯婆子
Monica::Really?
;真的?
Phoebe::Please.
;求你了
Monica::Do you really want me to come back?
;你真想让我回来?
Phoebe::Uh, more than I want to get married.
;嗯, 胜过我想结婚
Monica::Ok, people, we're back in business.
;好, 伙计们, 我们回来了
Monica::Oh god, I've missed you so much.
;哦天哪, 我可想死你了
Monica::Ok, go get you hair makeup done and I'll take care of everything.
;好, 去做你的头发吧这儿一切交给我好了
Joey::Hey, what are you guys gonna do?
;嘿, 你们打算怎么办?
Phoebe::About what? Joey::The blizzard.
;什么怎么办? 暴风雪啊
Joey::I just saw on the news said the worst snowstorm in 20 years already closed all the bridges and tunnels.
;刚才电视上说这是20年来最大的一场暴风雪 所有的桥和隧道都关闭了
Monica::But the band and photographer are coming all the way from New Jersey.
;可是乐队和摄像师还要从新泽西赶过来呢！
Joey::I don't think they are.
;看来他们够呛
Ross::Ha ha, looks you're not gonna be in the wedding, either.
;哈哈, 看起来你恐怕也参加不了仪式了吧
Ross::So sorry, Phoebs.
;真遗憾啊, Phoebe
Monica::Well, the club lost its power.
;俱乐部停电了
Joey::Yeah, according to the news, most of the city did.
;是啊，听新闻说，市里大部分地区都停电了
Rachel::Since when do you watch the news?
;你从什么时候开始看起新闻来了?
Joey::Uh, F.Y.I, since they hired a very hot weather girl.
;呃，告诉你好了，从那个靓女开始主持天气预报的时候
Ross::I can't believe you guys aren't gonna be bale to get married today.
;真不敢相信，你们两个今天的婚礼办不成了
Rachel::Well, you know, it's so beautiful out there.
;哇，你们看哪，外面真的好美
Rachel::You always wanted to get married outside, why don't you guys just do it on the street?
;你不是总想在户外举行婚礼吗？ 你们俩干嘛不干脆在街上结婚呢？
Rachel::What?
;什么?
Rachel::Look, it's hardly snowing anymore.
;看哪，雪几乎已经停了
Rachel::I mean, you couldn't ask for a more romantic setting.
;我想，没有比这更加浪漫的布景了
Rachel::This could be the simple wedding you've always wanted.
;这不正是你一直想要的简单的婚礼吗？
Phoebe::What do you think?
;你认为呢?
Mike::I think I wanted to get married to you today.
;我只想今天就跟你结婚
Phoebe::Me, too.
;我也是
Phoebe::Monica, do you think we can do it?
;Monica, 你觉得这样可行吗?
Monica::Affirmative.
;赞成
Monica::Ok. Let's get these chairs out here.
;好 大家把椅子都搬出来
Monica::Gunther, hit the christmas lights.
;Gunther, 把圣诞用的灯饰都打亮
Monica::Ok, who left the ice sculpture on the steam grid?
;好, 是哪个家伙把冰雕放在热水井旁边的?
Mike's mom::Michael. Mike::Hey, you made it. Great.
;Michael 嘿, 你们来了太好了
Mike::Chappy!
;Chappy!
Mike::Mom, I know getting married in the street isn't sth you approve of...
;妈妈, 我知道在大街上结婚这种事 肯定不合你的脾气...
Mike's mom::No. It's lovely, the lights and the snow. I can look at them forever.
;不，这挺有趣儿的，又是灯又是雪的 我怎么看都看不够
Mike's dad::I crashed the pill and put it in her drink.
;我刚才在她的饮料里下了点药
Mike's dad::Come on, sweat heart.
;来吧, 亲爱的
Mike::You know, Chappy is too small to handle all the snow,
;你们看, Chappy太弱小了， 它恐怕难以应付这一地的积雪
Mike::someone's gonna have to walk him down the aisle.
;到时候需要有人抱着它
Chandler::So, technically will this person be in the wedding?
;那么, 就定义来说，这个人也算 参加了婚礼仪式吧?
Mike::I guess. Chandler and Ross::I'll do it.
;我想是吧 我来
Ross::Wait, no. But Chandler, hello, aren't you scared of dogs?
;等等，Chandler，hello, 你不是害怕狗吗?
Chandler::I'm not scared. I just take little Chappy and...
;谁说我害怕我只要抱着小Chappy，然后...
Chandler::He can sense my fear! My throat is exposed!
;它知道我害怕它! 我的嗓子都翻出来了!
Ross::Oh, I guess I'm in the wedding, then. Ha ha!
;哦, 那么我猜 出现在婚礼上的人就是我喽 哈哈
Ross::He stinks.
;它好臭
Monica::Level 1 alert! I repeat, Level 1, this is not a drill!
;一级警报! 重复, 一级警报, 这不是演习!
Monica::We've got a situation, the minister just called he's snowed in, he can't make it.
;我们碰到难题了, 牧师刚才打电话来说 他被大雪困住，赶不过来了
Mike::Oh, no.
;哦，不是吧
Joey::Oh hey, don't worry. I'm still ordained from your wedding.
;嘿, 甭担心我在你们结婚那会儿获得 的牧师资格到现在还有效
Monica::Really? Joey::Yeah.
;真的? 是啊
Joey::You think I'd give up being a minister and start paying the ride of subway?
;你认为我会放弃牧师资格吗？ 那样的话我坐地铁就不能免票了
Ross::Uh, ministers don't ride the subway for free.
;呃, 牧师坐地铁也不能免票的
Joey::I had to read the bible pretty carefully, but yeah, we do.
;我仔细研究过圣经的, 没错，我们不用买票
Monica::Ok, if Joey does the ceremony, then we have to find someone else to walk Phoebe down the aisle.
;好, 如果让Joey来主持婚礼的话, 那我们还需要有个人来挽着Phoebe
Chandler::I'll do it! Aha ha...
;我来! 啊哈哈...
Monica::Ok, Mike and Joey, get in position. Chandler, come with me.
;好, Mike和Joey, 各就各位 Chandler, 跟我来
Monica::Ok, Joey's throwing the ceremony, and Chandler's giving you away.
;好, Joey负责主持婚礼, 你由Chandler负责
Phoebe::Oh, ok. Hi, new dad.
;哦, 好嗨, 新爹
Monica::So, you ready to do this?
;那么, 你准备好了么?
Phoebe::Uh uhn. Oh my god, this is really happening.
;哦，天哪，这一切都是真的
Rachel::Oh, Phoebe, I'm so happy for you, honey.
;哦, Phoebe, 我真替你高兴, 亲爱的
Monica::I love you.
;我爱你
Monica::Oh, wait wait, no hugs, the dresses! What the hell.
;等等，不要抱，当心礼服! 管它的.
Come on!
;来吧!
Phoebe::I love you, guys.
;我爱你们，亲爱的
Monica::Ok, it's 0:00. All teams execute on my count.
;好, 现在是0:00各小组听我的指令行事
Monica::Let's get this bad boy on the road!
;我们开始吧!
Chandler::Is it ok that I want you to wear that headset in bed tonight?
;我想让你今晚戴着这副耳机上床，你不反对吧?
Monica::Uh, I have the schedule for nudity at 23:00.
;呃, 根据计划，我的裸体时间被安排在23:00
Chandler::Oh yeah.
;噢耶
Monica::Ok, Margery, hit it.
;好, Margery, 开始敲你的吧
Rachel::Geeze, Ross, you could've showered.
;天哪, Ross, 你就不能先洗个澡吗
Ross::It's the dog!
;是狗身上的味!
Monica::Groomsman, why are you just stading there? Where's your bridesmaid?
;伴郎, 为什么只有你一个人站在这儿? 伴娘呢?
Monica::We've got a broken error, bridesmaid down.
;我们遇到情况了, 伴娘失踪了
Monica::Oh, it's me.
;噢, 是我自己
Chandler::Ready? Chandler::Ok.
;准备好了么? 好
Phoebe::Oh wait, oh no, wait.
;哦, 等一下, 哦, 等等
Chandler::Wow, aren't you gonna be could?
;哇, 你不觉得冷吗?
Phoebe::I don't care. I'll be my sth blue.
;我不在乎我要做自己的 “something blue”（象征新娘纯洁的宝物）
Chandler::You look beautiful. Phoebe::Thank you.
;你看起来美极了 谢谢
Mike::My god, aren't you freezing?
;天哪，你不冷吗?
Phoebe::Nuh.
;不
Joey::Friends, Family, Dog.
;朋友们，家人们，狗儿
Joey::Thank you all for been here to witness this blessed event.
;们能够到场来见证这一场天赐的姻缘
Joey::The could has now spread to my special place.
;冷空气已经蔓延到我“那里”了
Joey::So I'm gonna do the short version of this.
;所以我会长话短说
Joey::Phoebe and Mike are perfect for each other and I know I speak for everyone here
;Phoebe和Mike是完美的一对儿 我相信在场的每一个人都会和我一样
Joey::when I wish them a lifetime of happiness.
;祝愿他们一生幸福
Joey::Who has the rings?
;戒指?
Phoebe::When I was growing up, I didn't have a normal mom and dad,
;在我成长的过程中, 我不曾拥有真正的父爱和母爱
Phoebe::or a regular family like everybody else.
;或者和别人一样拥有一个正常的家庭
Phoebe::And I always knew that something was missing.
;我总是觉得自己缺少了些什么
Phoebe::But now, I'm standing here today,
;然而现在, 我站在这里,
Phoebe::knowing that I have the everything I'm ever gonna need:
;我知道自己已经得到了自己所需要的一切
Phoebe::You are my family.
;你就是我的家人
Mike::Phoebe, you're so beautiful. You're so kind, you're so generous.
;Phoebe, 你是这么的美丽，这么的善良， 这么的大方
Mike::You're so wonderfully weird.
;古怪的你是那么的迷人
Mike::Every day with you is an adventure.
;和你在一起的每一天都像是一次探险
Mike::I can't believe how lucky I am.
;我简直不敢相信自己是如此地幸运
Mike::And I can't wait to share my life with you forever.
;我迫不急待地想要和你分享自己的生命， 直到永远
Phoebe::Oh wait, no. I forgot, and I love you.
;哦等一下，我忘了说，我爱你
Phoebe::And you have nice eyes.
;还有，你的眼睛很漂亮
Mike::I love you, too.
;我也爱你
Ross::Uh, Joey. Chppy's heart rate has slowed way down.
;呃, JoeyChppy的心脏越跳越慢了
Joey::Phoebe, do you take this man to be your husband?
;Phoebe, 你愿意这个男人成为你的丈夫吗?
Phoebe::I do.
;我愿意
Joey::Mike, do you take this woman to be your wife?
;Mike, 你愿意这个女人成为你的妻子吗?
Mike::I do.
;我愿意
Joey::I now pronounce you husband and wife.
;我现在正式宣布你们结为夫妻
Phoebe::I got married!
;我结婚了!
Phoebe::Could someone get me a coat? I'm frigging freezing.
;谁递给我件衣服? 我快要冻僵了
Chandler::That really was an incredible wedding.
;真是场让人难以置信的婚礼
Joey::That was, yeah. I kinda don't want to end.
;是啊，的确我真不想让它就那么结束
Joey::Hey, you wanna come in for a drink and bite a corsage?
;嘿, 你想来喝一杯吗，还有一些襟花可以吃
Joey::I'd love to but it's 23:00 and I'm about to have the most organized sex anyone's ever had.
;我很想去，但现在已经23:00了，我现在要去 经历一次有史以来最有组织的性爱
Joey::Nice. Hey, what happened to Ross?
;好样的嘿, Ross呢?
Joey::I don't know. Maybe he hooked up with that hot girl he was talking to.
;我不知道刚才他还在跟一个辣妹聊天来着， 大概两个人搞在一起了吧
Joey::Come on, Chappy, do your business, make!
;快点, Chappy, 拜托你快点解决了吧, 拉啊!
Joey::I did not sign on for this.
;我参加婚礼可不是为了做这个